Hey, you guys.
Hey.
Hey. What are you doing?
Oh, figuring out
our wedding plans.
That's funny. We were
doing the same thing.
Yeah.
It's really crazy.
The hall,
the dress, the food--
I-I had no idea
how expensive this stuff was.
Yeah, it's really pricey.
I mean, I freaked
when I first heard the numbers.
So what did you two
do about it?
It's pretty simple actually.
I came up with a couple
cost-cutting solutions,
wrote out a list, and Monica
told me to go to hell.
ROSS:
There is no way
around it.
Pheebs, you're just going
have to accept the fact
that this is going to
cost you a lot of money.
I heard the weddings are like
a $40-billion-a-year industry.
Yeah, and I'm responsible
for just like half of that.
But, really, it does
seem like this money
could be put
to better use.
Are you serious?
Yeah. Now,
how would you feel
if we gave
all the wedding money
to charity, and-and we just
got married at City Hall?
I figured it would make me
want to marry you even more.
I've got to say,
you guys,
that's, that's
an incredible gesture.
Maybe you'd do that
next time you get married.
No, no, no.
The next time it's going
to be Hawaii at sunset.
But maybe the time after that.
Captioning sponsored by
WARNER BROS. TELEVISION
and NBC
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hey.
What's going on?
Our adoption social worker's
coming by today,
so we're cleaning the apartment.
"We"?
You know
you don't want me to help.
You can't have it both ways.
Hey, is this the
person who decides
whether or not you get a baby?
Kind of. She's coming by
to interview us
and see where we live.
And it has to go perfectly
because if she doesn't like
something about us,
she can keep us off every
adoption list in the state.
Hey, maybe
I should stop by.
She could be a soap opera fan.
It's very impressive when the
little people know a celebrity.
Little people?
Celebrity.
Okay, so I think
I'm just about done here,
unless you have any bad stuff
hidden somewhere,
like porn or cigarettes?
What?!
No!
Chandler?
I don't, and I'm offended
by the insinuation.
Okay.
So there's not a magazine
under the couch?
Or a pack of cigarettes taped
to the back of a toilet tank?
Or a filthy video
in the VCR?
I'll admit to
the cigarettes
and the magazine,
but that tape is not mine.
Well, it isn't mine.
Oh, I guess we'll never know
whose it is.
May I help you?
Yes. We're here
to make a rather
sizable donation
to the children.
Well, any contribution large
or small is always appreciated.
Well, I think you're
going to appreciate
the crap out of this one.
Well, this is very generous.
And we don't want
any recognition.
This is completely anonymous.
Completely anonymous.
From two kind strangers.
Mr. X and Phoebe Buffay.
Oh, if you like, we can
include your names
in our newsletter.
Not necessary.
Buffay is spelled B-U-F-F-A-Y.
And X is spelled...
Mike Hannigan.
All right, well, on behalf
of the children,
thank you both very much.
Sure. I'm so glad
we did this.
It feels so good.
It does, it feels
really good.
Oh, look,
and we get these
free T-shirts!
Actually, that's the shirt
I wore to the gym.
Mm, it's moist.
Rach.
Hi!
Emma will be up in a minute.
Oh, good.
Oh, hey, Ross, listen, I heard
about you and Charlie.
I'm really sorry.
Aw, that's okay.
I'm sure there are
tons of other beautiful
paleontologists out there.
Absolutely.
There was one! She's it!
All the rest look like they
should live under a bridge!
So, uh, what are you
going to do today?
Oh, I was thinking of taking
Emma to the playground.
Oh, my God. What?
Like I said, I was thinking
of taking Emma to the Museum
of Knives and Fire.
Okay, look, Ross,
I do not
want Emma going
to the playground.
Because...
All right, well,
if you must know,
I had a traumatic swing incident
when I was little.
Seriously?
Yes. I was four years old,
and I was on the swing,
and then all of a sudden,
my hair got tangled
in the chain...
And to get me out,
my mom had to,
had to cut a big
chunk of my hair.
( choked up ):
And it was uneven for weeks.
( sniffling )
And you made it through that?
I wonder who's going
to play you in the movie.
Okay, fine, you can
make fun of me,
I do not want Emma going there.
And I was thinking Claire Danes.
Look, I'm sorry to hear
about your tragedy,
okay, but the swings
are perfectly safe.
And besides,
Emma loves them.
You know what? You should
come with us and you'll see.
Ross, those things go,
like, 40 miles an hour!
Okay, when you're at this
moment, when you're at the top,
when you just don't know
if you're going to
return back to Earth.
Space is filled with
orbiting children.
Look, please, just...
just come on.
You know what? When you see
the look on Emma's face,
I swear, you won't regret it.
All right.
Good.
You know, you don't want
to be one of those mothers
who pass on their irrational
fears to their children, do you?
Irrational, huh?
All right, well, I'll remember
that the next time
you freak out about a spider
in your apartment.
Oh, yeah, that's the same.
I'm sure there are 30 different
species of poisonous swings.
( knock at door )
Oh, my God,
the adoption lady's early.
Okay, okay.
Here we go,
here we go.
Okay.
Stand up straight.
Big smile.
Hello. Is this
the Creepy residence?
We're waiting for
the adoption lady.
But hey, I'm glad you're here.
I was cleaning this morning,
and I found this.
Now, I don't know
if you want to use it, but...
Oh, this is
so sweet of you.
Oh, but you know what?
I won't be needing a veil.
I actually won't be
wearing a dress at all.
I told you, I am not coming
to a naked wedding.
No, no, no,
we're just... we're not
having a big reception.
We took the money we're gonna
spend on the wedding,
and we donated it
to a children's charity.
That's crazy!
I'm sorry. I just...
I can't imagine giving up
my one wedding day like that.
Yeah, well, we're different,
you know.
I don't care about
having a huge party.
This is really
nice for you,
but, oh, please,
I put this on
and ugh, I just look like...
well, radiant.
All right, but who cares?
You know, I don't need
a pretty veil and a fancy dress.
That's right, you're making
a commitment and, you know,
that's the same whether
you do it at the Plaza or...
Where are you going to do it?
City Hall.
Oh!
Oh, that sounds nice.
Well, I was just there
for jury duty.
They really spruced
that place up.
Okay. No, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
I made my decision.
What I really want
is a great big wedding.
Yay!
But you already gave
all the money to charity.
Well, just ask for it back.
I don't think you can do that.
Why not?
This is her wedding day.
That's way more important
than some stupid kids.
That's sweet, honey, but save
something for the adoption lady.
RACHEL:
Okay.
Here we go.
All right, okay,
be careful.
Okay.
Be careful.
Watch her hair.
Watch her hair!
Rach, she's got,
like, three hairs.
I know.
I know, but they're
just so beautiful.
Oh, my God, I just
pulled one out!
I promise you,
she's safe, okay?
Now watch. Watch how
much she loves this.
Okay, okay.
Are you ready,
sweetie?
Here we go.
Okay, careful.
( cooing )
'Kay.
Oh.
( cooing )
Oh!
She's smiling.
Oh, look at that!
She just likes it.
See? I told you.
Oh... oh.
Oh!
( giggling )
Oh, my God!
Look at her, she's
a little daredevil!
Oh, God, oh,
let me push.
Can I push?
Oh, absolutely.
Okay.
Oh, gosh.
Okay, get the camera.
It's in the diaper bag.
Okay.
See?
Scared of the swings.
I bet you'll feel pretty silly.
( screams )
( yells )
We're seriously asking
for the money back?
It's for our
wedding day.
All right, now, is this
guy gay or straight?
'Cause one of us's gonna
have to start flirting.
Wow! You're here to make
another donation the same day?
I don't think that's
ever happened before.
Gay. Go.
Oh, my God,
I love your shirt.
All right.
The donation we made earlier,
um, well, we... we want,
we want it back.
Excuse me?
Yeah, see, okay, that
money was for, um,
a big wedding that we
thought we didn't want.
But it turns out we do.
So, you're asking us to refund
your donation to the children?
Yeah.
This feels really good.
Yeah, I'm sor... I'm sorry,
I am, but you know,
this wedding's just
really important to me.
It's none of my business.
Besides, this is
probably a good thing.
We've really been spoiling
the children,
what with all the food
and warm clothing.
That's not fair.
A person's wedding is important,
and especially to me.
Okay? I-I didn't have
a graduation party
and I didn't go to prom.
And I spent my sweet 16
being chased around a tire yard
by an... escaped mental patient
who, in his own words,
wanted to kill me or whatever.
So, I deserve
a real celebration,
and-and-and I'm not gonna
let some sweaty little man
make me feel
badly about it.
She could have been talking
about either one of us.
( knock at door )
Hi. I'm Laura.
I'm here for your
adoption interview.
Hi. I'm Monica.
And this is Chandler.
Hi.
Please come in.
Thank you.
Would you like
something to drink?
Oh, water
would be fine.
Okay, great.
We're so glad
that you're here.
We're really excited about
getting this process started.
Because we love kids.
Love 'em to death.
Well, not actually to death.
That's just a figure of speech.
We love kids
the appropriate amount.
As allowed by law.
Your place is just lovely.
Oh, thank you.
Yes, this building does have
a wholesome family feel to it.
You know, I-I feel like
I've been here before.
Are any other couples
in the building adopting?
Is that-that couple
on the first floor?
Because we should get a baby
before them.
Yeah, that guy tried
to sell me drugs!
But other than that,
wholesome...
wholesome building.
Oh...
What?
I just realized why
I remember this place.
Really? What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
I went on a date with a guy
who lived in this building.
It didn't end very well.
That wouldn't by any chance
be Joey Tribbiani?
Yes!
Of course it was.
Yeah, we had
a really great night
and in the morning, he promised
he would call me and he didn't.
Rat bastard!
So you're not friends with him?
Oh, God, no!
Nope. No, no, no.
No.
No, nope.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no.
No!
No.
Well, I'm sorry I brought it up.
So, are either one of you
planning on staying at home?
( knock at door )
JOEY:
Hello?!
Anybody in there?
Order a celebrity?
Ow!
Wh-What's that?
Oh, it's just some crazy guy
who roams the halls here.
He's great with kids, though.
Oh, God, Ross!
Oh, my God!
Are you okay?
Son of a bitch!
Oh, relax.
I didn't say the F-word!
Ross, see?
I told you those
swings are evil!
All right,
that is it.
That is the last time
Emma is getting on
one of those things
for her entire life.
No! No, no, no, no.
Okay, it wasn't
the swing's fault.
It was my fault...
and kind of
that kid's fault.
Who is still laughing.
Nice.
Ross, come on, please.
Could we just get
out of here
before somebody else
gets hurt?
No, wait-- okay, okay,
I have an idea.
I want you to get
on the swing, okay,
and you'll see that
there's nothing
to be afraid of.
I know what this
is all about.
You've always been
jealous of my hair.
Look, I just think
you're an adult, okay?
And you should get over
your silly fears.
All right, fine.
I'll do it.
Good.
If you hold a spider.
What?! Where?! Where?!
I know.
( groans )
JOEY:
Guys! Is everything okay?
It's me, Joey!
( screams )
Aah... gumption!
What's going on?
Oh, just like I said,
that crazy...
Bert...
roaming the halls.
( pounding )
Guys!
Keep on roaming, Bert!
We don't want
any crazy today!
JOEY:
What's going on?
We'll talk to you later,
Bert.
Everything's fine!
Everything doesn't sound fine.
Is he all right,
out there by himself?
Oh, yeah.
He has a caretaker.
His older brother...
Ernie.
Bert and Ernie.
You can't make this stuff up.
You never told me about
that guy and your Sweet 16.
Ugh! I'm sorry about that.
Oh, it ended okay.
One of my friends
shot him.
Well, hey, at least you're
getting a proper wedding.
I mean, you really
deserve that.
Yeah, I really do.
You know, I had nothing
growing up.
Just like the kids
I took the money from.
No.
No, no, I see
where this is going.
Don't make me
go back there.
Look, I can't have a wedding
with this money now.
It's tainted.
All right, fine.
We'll give the money back.
And if that guy at the charity
gives us a hard time,
my friend hasn't shot anyone
in a really long time.
Well, I must say
this seems like
a lovely environment
to raise a child in.
Oh, by the way, you
are more than welcome
to look under any
of the furniture,
because, believe me,
you won't find any
porn or cigarettes
under there.
Oh, thanks.
Well, actually,
before we look around,
let me make sure I have
everything I need up to here.
Why don't I show you
the baby's room?
What the hell
are you doing?
Well, you wouldn't
let me in,
so I thought
you were in trouble!
Well, we're not!
But you called me Bert!
That's our code word
for "danger."
We don't have a code word.
We don't?!
We really should.
From now on, "Bert" will be
our code word for danger.
So that was the
baby's room...
Uh, what room
should we see next?
Any room that isn't
behind this couch.
( forced laughter )
Some people don't get him,
but I think
he's really funny.
I did not care
for that.
You have to get
out of here.
You slept with
our social worker,
and you never
called her back,
and she is still
pissed, so she
can't see you.
Oh, okay, okay, okay.
What?!
I forgot my bat.
Oh, my God!
And for the last time,
we do not want to be
friends with you!
And we don't want
to buy your bat!
What are you doing here?
Bert, Bert, Bert,
Bert...
Are you friends with him?
I can explain.
Joey?
Uh, okay, uh...
Oh, yeah... you have got
some nerve coming back here.
I can't believe
you never called me.
Excuse me?!
Oh! Yeah!
Probably don't even
remember my name!
It's Joey, by the way.
And don't bother
telling me yours,
because I totally remember it...
lady.
Yeah.
I waited weeks
for you to call me!
I gave you my number;
you never called me.
Don't try to turn this around
on me, okay?
I am not some... kind of...
social work, okay,
that you can just... do.
Well, I'm pretty sure
I gave you my number.
Really?
Think about it.
Come on.
You're a beautiful woman,
smart,
funny.
We had a really
good time, huh?
If I had your number,
why wouldn't I call you?
I don't know.
Well, maybe I'm wrong.
I'm sorry.
No, no, hey, no.
Too late for apologies, okay?
You broke my heart.
You know how many women I had
to sleep with to get over you?
Joey, wait!
No!
I waited a long time.
I can't wait anymore.
I'm sorry that
you had to see that.
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh, that's really okay.
Yeah, and we
totally understand.
Dating is hard!
Boy, you people
are nice.
( laughs )
And I've got to say...
I think you're going to make
excellent parents.
Laura!
( door slams )
We're back.
Are you here
to take more money?
Because I think what you're
looking for is an ATM.
No, no, we're here
to give the money back.
Yeah, 'cause, you
know what, it's...
it's all about the children.
Although...
it's also about the wedding.
Ugh. All right. Here.
No. Oh, God! Oh...
If I haven't said so already,
sir-- congratulations.
Okay, look, enough.
All right?
I'm stepping in.
I'm putting my foot down.
As your future husband,
I'm going to make this
decision for us.
Okay.
W-What do you think
we should do?
You know what?
It's not your decision anymore.
What?!
On behalf
of the children
of New York,
I reject your money.
B-But we're giving you this.
Yeah, and I'm giving it
back to you.
Come on.
Consider it a contribution.
Well, this is
very generous.
Please, take the check.
Go have a great wedding
and a wonderful life together.
Well, I mean,
it sounds good to me.
And that way, we can save up,
come back in a few years,
and make an even bigger
donation.
Absolutely.
And when you do,
make sure you ask for Brian.
Oh, is that you?
No.
( phone rings )
Hello.
Oh, hi.
Oh, my God!
Really?
I can't wait to
tell Chandler.
Okay. Good-bye.
Wrong number?
That was Laura.
She gave us
a great report
and we are officially
on the waiting list.
That's great!
Now we just have
to wait for a call
and someone tells
us there's a baby
waiting for us.
Oh!
Aw...
( phone ringing )
Hello?
Have you seen Joey's bat?
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
Okay. I got a spider.
There were two.
I picked the bigger one.
Okay...
Okay.
( gasps )
This feels perfectly normal.
Okay, get on the swing.
Okay...
O... kay...
Okay.
Oop. Okay.
( whimpers )
Oh!
See?
Oh, all right.
I can do this.
There you go!
Good for you!
And you know what?
I'm actually getting used
to this little guy.
I don't really even
feel him in here anymore.
That's 'cause he's
on your neck.
( shrieking )
Oh, my God!
Oh! Ross! Ross!